Hello everyone welcome back to our post square SQL tutorials. We so today we're going to explore for some common operator
Using the post-way SQL for coding and manipulating data, okay?
So first of all simply explain for the operator singer post-care SQL, okay?
So the post-care SQL allows us to perform various operations on data centers comparison arithmetic and the logical operations
Okay, so I hope you have to plan to understand this operation is essentially for identifying the
effective SQL query, okay? So in this session for the
post-care SQL
The several comparison. So first of all here, let me create the comparison. The operator is defined.
So the comparison operator include for the equal less than greater than
equal to and less than equal to and more and in this session explain for simply greater than
operator, it's okay.
So here use for
the employee stable and here the employee stable all for the
use for the greater than operator, okay?
So here first of all the select and
This style and the table name suppose here the second check is the employees, okay?
So
Employees and then the next step and here use for the multiple
Use for the defined for the ages
Greater than
25, okay, so now here define perfectly and here I can completely using for the greater than
And select all the employees and here
Implicitable for the ages greater than 25, okay?
So here I can select all the data query and the next queue and you can see here this is
greater than
27, 29, 32 and 35, okay, so here choosing for the
30 and
Then again select and execute and just wait and you can see here the
24 greater than 22 and the 25, okay?
So here this is completely operation successful and the post-care schedule will return the matching row as the result
Say, okay?
So now I'll create for another person like the arithmetic operators, okay?
So you can see here I can describe for the arithmetic operator, so just go ahead the table for
select from and
So here I'll just move this, okay?
And first of all, I can type for the select and the salary, okay? So here the salary column now
First of all, I can define for the salary use for the multiple sign, okay?
So next step here use for is one point is one, okay?
So here I can describe for use as statement for increased salary, okay?
So increase
And then underscore the
salary column, okay now here choose for the employees table, okay?
So here completely different and in this the multiple operator to multiply the salary column of the employees table
by one point one is
effectively increasing the salary by
these operations so now just select and all and then execute and in this order you can see here the
team for the salary is perfectly
added so you can see here the
employee stable and the salary range and
now here
And here is the main salary range and now use here
This is the one point one and here perfectly updated for
here is open for the new column for the employee stable here the employee salary, okay?
So here these are the possible ways for the return that calculate the value of the operator
So you can collect and use for another operator suppose like the logical operator
So the logical operator allows us to combine multiple conditions using the and or and not a part, okay?
So here I can only use for the end operator, okay?
So now just going for here and first of all I can use for select the start from the employee stable
and going to our next step here I can use for the y
plus eight and greater than
joining
seven, okay?
And here use the end operator and then type for real the department so use the department
of the equal to, so now the stair type for the department of the age, okay?
So now here simply define and then and then I'll just select all the employees for the employee stable
where is age is greater than 27 and
population is successful, okay?
So now here select and execute now you can see here now where different for the age is 30
and then check for the age and verify and use the same person just going for greater than
for simply here use the so now going for here again and this is and
the department for so here use for the next sign use and then just select and execute now, okay?
And you can see here this is the i-day for two and first name then
the zero and the age is 27 and the department of age, okay?
And perfectly now see the output and here the person is successful and the
most true return the matching row as the result, okay?
So you can choose here so now here is for all operators and then just select for execute and
you can see here the output for the IT department, HR department then the marketing department
and then less than 25 is 27 and that's only nine, okay?
So here in this session is completely done and here perfectly used for the post clear SQL
operators. So I hope you understand this session so thank you for watching and happy coding.